aaa
i said this time next year
i'mma be the one who do everything and more
you said i couldn't do this one's for you
this time next year i'm gonna be stronger
a little bit taller top is my only view
oh oh oh i'm kicking in the door now better get out my way
never really saw me coming
you're left with nothing to say
this for everybody who'd always put me down
i hope you open up your eyes and take a good look at me now
take a good look at me now
take a good look at me now'cause this time next year
i'mma walk down these halls
and show my face for the world to see
gonna see me
and i'ma call every girl that turn me down
and tell him now
that i'm just too busy'cause i don't have the time
and it's funny how my soul called friends
who'd always left me alone
or suddenly running into me and blowing up my phone
i'm kicking in the door now better get out my way
never really saw me coming
you left with nothing to say
this for everybody who'd always put me down
i hope you open up your eyes and take a good look at me now
take a good look at me now
oh baby take a good look at me now
now take a good look at me now
oh look at me now
oh
this one is dedicated to all of the people
who said i would be nothing
just look at me now
look at me now look at me now
i'm kicking in the door now
better get out my way
never really saw me coming
you left with nothing to say
this for everybody who'd always put me down
i hope you open up your eyes and take a good look at me now
take a girl look at me now